Hello, everyone, and welcome to a very, very special edition of This Just In.
My name is Marco.
And I'm Erica.
And today we're going to be informing you on some really great and special news.
That's right.
We are going to have a live English pod conference.
Right, a video conference.
Yes.
So you are going to be able to see us and listen to us live from your computer.
And talk to us.
That's the great thing.
Yeah.
We're going to be able to interact with you.
And text us your messages.
We can be chatting live.
Yep.
And also, if you have webcams or headsets, we can also listen to you.
Okay, so Marco, what are we going to do in this conference?
Okay, in this conference, we are going to go over this week's lessons.
That's right.
Just talk about some of the vocabulary, any doubts, any questions that our users might
have.
Yep.
And you have some tasks that they are going to be doing, right?
That's right.
And you have some tasks where you can actually practice with the new language with us and
with other English pod users.
Right.
So it's going to be a really interesting conference because we are not going to be
the only ones talking or teaching, also other more advanced users as well.
So we're going to take the classroom onto the web.
Onto the web.
Okay.
So, Marco, when is this conference?
Okay, this conference is on Friday, December 19th.
Okay.
What time?
We're going to have two of them.
Okay.
One is at 10 a.m. and the other one is at 5 p.m.
And that's Beijing time, right?
Beijing time, yes.
So that's GMT plus eight.
Plus eight.
So you have to more or less see what's the difference in your country.
Maybe in Europe, it'll be a little bit earlier or later.
I don't know how that works.
Okay, figure out the time.
We're going to be there at 10 a.m. and at 5 p.m.
5 p.m.
Okay.
I'll post a link to the website where you have to go.
You don't have to download any software.
That's right.
You can just go click on this link where you'll be invited to attend the meeting with us.
Now something very important.
Now listen carefully.
We have a limit for 20 people.
That's right.
Only 20 can attend.
Right.
So, it's going to be on a first come, first serve basis.
So the first 20 people that come in get to attend the conference.
That's right.
So if you want to attend, you better be there early.
Right.
The early bird gets the worm, right?
That's the saying.
Okay.
So we'll keep you updated.
And if you have any questions, please send us a message and we'll be happy to answer.
And I'm really looking forward to meeting some of our listeners on the web.
Yeah.
It'll be exciting.
Okay.
This is all for today.
Be sure to attend our conference on Friday.
And until then, it's...
Goodbye.
Bye.
EnglishPod.com.